Kheel, Theodore W. Non-Profit Organization Files 6021/006
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Foundation on Employee Health, Medical Care, and Welfare, Inc., 1956-1962 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Annual Meeting
- Foundation on Employee Health, Medical Care, and Welfare, Inc. Miscellaneous, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Institute of Collective Bargaining and Group Relations - Center for Mediation and Confl. Res. - Ford Grant Copp., 1971 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Center for Mediation and Conflict Resolution, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Center for Mediation and Conflict Resolution, 1969-1972 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Institute of Collective Bargaining and Group Relations - Conference, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Institute of Collective Bargaining and Group Relations - Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Institute of Collective Bargaining and Group Relations, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Institute of Collective Bargaining - Study of Apprenticeship Prog., Newsp. - Union Study Group (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Institute of Collective Bargaining and Group Relations, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Institute of Collective Bargaining - Newspaper/Union Study Group, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Institute of Collective Bargaining and Group Relations/Automation House, 1972-1975 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Music des Arts Decoratifs - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Musei des Arts Decoratfis - Corresp. Copies, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Musee des Arts Decoratifs - Cert. of Amendment, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Musee des Arts Decoratifs - Resolution and Bylaws, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Musee des Arts Decoratifs - Draft of Janicot Letter, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Musee Des Arts Decoratifs - Description, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Musee des Arts Paris Decoratifs Arts Museum Foundation - Certificate of Inc., 1983 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Musee des Arts Decoratifs - Museum Industries, Inc., 1985 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Musee des Arts Decoratifs - Other Museums, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Musee des Arts Decoratifs - potential Contributors, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Musee des Arts Union Central des Arts Decoratifs Cert. of Inc., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Musee des Arts Decoratifs - News Articles, 1981-1985 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Musee des Arts Decoratifs - Russell Blair, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Musee des Arts Decoratifs - Robert Bordaz, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Musee des Arts Decoratifs - Fundraising/Program Activity, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Musee des Arts Decoratifs - Le Grand Diner, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Punta Cana Sustainable Seminar, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Punta Cana Lawsuit, 1970-1985 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Punta Cana Lawsuit Title, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Punta Cana Lawsuit - Purchase of Property, 1970-1973 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Punta Cana Lawsuit - Decision, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Punta Cana Lawsuit - Misc. papers, 1970-1982 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Punta Cana Lawsuit Title, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Punta Cana Lawsuit - Purchase of Propert, 1970-1973 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Punta Cana Lawsuit - Decision, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Punta Cana Lawsuit - Misc. papers, 1970-1982 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Punta Cana - Michaan Loan - Promissory Notes, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Punta Cana - Michaan Loan - Corresp., 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Punta Cana, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Punta Cana Club Dominican Republic, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Punta Cana Clippings, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Punta Cana Clippings, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Punta Cana Clippings, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Punta Clippings, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Punta Cana Clippings, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Punta Cana Clippings, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Punta Cana - Clippings, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Satellite Public Interest Network (SPIN) (Box 7, Folder 23)
- SPIN Project Metro - Link, New TV Publication, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Theodore Kheel, Non-profit Org. (Box 8)